Sylvia Beach Papers, 1887-1966 (bulk 1920s-1950s ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
Sylvia Beach Papers
1872-1999
C0108
Princeton University. Library. Dept. of Rare Books and Special Collections Manuscripts Division One Washington Road Princeton, New Jersey 08544 USA
78.3 linear feet 180 boxes (17 oversize)
Beach, Sylvia.
This collection documents the life and activities of Sylvia Beach (1887-1962), the American author, publisher, and owner of the Paris bookshop Shakespeare & Company, the Paris bookshop that was a meeting-point for French, English, Irish and American writers during the 1920's and 1930's. The collection consists largely of files relating to Shakespeare & Company; Beach's writings and translations, in particular her memoir Shakespeare & Company; and files relating to the circle of artists and writers surrounding her throughout her life. Included are family, personal, and business correspondence; business records of Shakespeare & Company; personal and family records; manuscripts and artwork by members of her circle; photographs; and memorabilia.
Born in Baltimore, Maryland in 1887, Sylvia Beach was the second of three daughters of Eleanor Orbison Beach and the Reverend Sylvester Woodbridge Beach (Princeton Class of 1876), a pastor of the First Presbyterian Church in Princeton. She is best known for running the bookstore and lending library Shakespeare & Company and for publishing James Joyce's Ulysses.
With the help of Adrienne Monnier, owner of the bookshop La Maison des Amis des Livres, Beach opened Shakespeare & Company at at 8, Rue Dupuytren in Paris in 1919 as a bookshop, lending library, and occasional publisher specializing in English and American literature. In 1922 the shop moved to 12, Rue de l'Odéon, across the street from Monnier's establishment, where it remained until its closing in 1940. During two decades, Shakespeare & Company served as a meeting point for expatriate writers and American visitors to Paris. Beach was interned for six months during World War II, but although she managed to keep her inventory hidden in a vacant apartment nearby, she did not re-open the shop after the war.
Sylvia Beach chronicled her experiences with Shakespeare & Company and life in Paris between the wars in a memoir of the same title, Shakespeare and Company, which was published in 1956. Towards the end of her life, she was widely honored for her publication of Ulysses and her support of aspiring writers during the 1920s. She remained in Paris until her death in 1962. Her ashes were buried in the Beach family plot in Princeton, NJ.
This collection documents the life and activities of Sylvia Beach (1887-1962), the American author, publisher, and owner of Shakespeare & Company, the Paris bookshop that was a meeting-point for French, English, Irish and American writers during the 1920's and 1930's. The collection consists largely of files relating to Shakespeare & Company; Beach's writings and translations, in particular her memoir Shakespeare & Company; and files relating to the circle of artists and writers surrounding her throughout her life. Included are family, personal, and business correspondence; business records of Shakespeare & Company; personal and family records; manuscripts and artwork by members of her circle; photographs; and memorabilia.
The rich correspondence series consists of correspondence from and to Sylvia Beach and includes artists such as Hilda Doolittle, Ezra Pound, Sherwood Anderson, Gertrude Stein, Ernest Hemingway, Robert McAlmon, James Joyce, T. S. Eliot, William Carlos Williams, Allen Tate, Alice B. Toklas, Marianne Moore, Katherine Anne Porter, Richard Wright, George Antheil, Harriet Weaver, Gordon Craig, Arthur Symons, Ford Madox Ford, Frank Harris, Norman Douglas, Ivy Litvinoff, Richard Aldington, Stuart Gilbert, Cyril Connolly, D. H. Lawrence, Stephen Spender, Dorothy Richardson, to name but a few.
The collection also contains the files of Shakespeare & Company, Sylvia Beach's bookshop in Paris. Consisting largely of the shop's business records, the series notably contains the files of Shakespeare & Company's lending library, including member records and their readings. Of special interest is the material relating to Beach's publication of James Joyce, most importantly Joyce's Ulysses.
Also present is an extensive series of photographs documenting the different facets and relationships central to Beach's life, including family, friends, members of her artistic circle, and her life in Paris. They include snapshots as well as formal portraits, many of them captioned, and a number of them by noted photographers such as Gisèle Freund and Man Ray.
The collection further includes materials relating to Sylvia Beach's own writings and translations; artworks and literary manuscripts collected by her both for their artistic value and out of her interest in the artists; files relating to her personal life and files created by and relating to members of her family; and memorabilia.
Arranged into the following series: Series 1: Correspondence; Series 2: Shakespeare & Company; Series 3: Writings and Translations; Series 4: Personal Records; Series 5: Family Records; Series 6: Sylvia Beach's Circle and Collections; Series 7: Photographs; Series 8: Memorabilia
Access to the photographs is restricted because surrogates are available for reference use. Researchers who feel they have a compelling reason to be granted access to the original photographs must request permission in advance from the Curator of Manuscripts ( http://rbsc.princeton.edu/divisions/manuscripts-division ).
Original Hemingway is restricted. Surrogates are available for use.
The collection, which had remained in Miss Beach's Paris apartment at 12, Rue de l'Odéon since her death there in October 1962, was acquired in 1964 from the Sylvia Beach estate, through the generosity of Graham D. Mattison, Princeton Class of 1926, and with the interest and support of Miss Beach's surviving sister, Mrs. Frederic J. (Holly Beach) Dennis of Greenwich, Connecticut.
AM 18348
Individual items that were originally acquired as part of the Sylvia Beach Papers are now curated by the Graphic Arts division, including the Shakespeare & Company shop sign painted by Marie Monnier-Bécat; a portrait of Sylvia Beach in oil by Paul-Émile Bécat, signed, Paris, 1923; and a full-length portrait of Adrienne Monnier in oil by Paul-Émile Bécat, Paris 1921
In addition, two items that remain part of the Sylvia Beach Papers are: an oak cabinet and a bust of William Shakespeare executed in colored Staffordshireware.
Other major collections of Sylvia Beach material are housed at the University of Buffalo and the Harry Ransom Center at the University of Texas, Austin.
"The Sylvia Beach Collection" by Howard C. Rice, Jr., The Princeton University Library Chronicle, Vol. XXVI, No. 1 (Autumn, 1964). pp. 7-15.
Joyce, James, 1882-1941 -- Publishers.; Joyce, James, 1882-1941. Ulysses.; Shakespeare & Company (Paris, France).; Authors and publishers -- France -- 20th century.; Authors, American -- France -- 20th century.; Authors, English -- France -- 20th century.; Authors, French -- 20th century.; Authors, Irish -- France -- 20th century.; Booksellers and bookselling -- France -- Paris -- 20th century -- Biography.; Bookstores -- France -- Paris -- 20th century.; Exiles' writings -- 20th century.; Novelists, American -- France -- 20th century.; Novelists, English -- France -- 20th century.; Novelists, Irish -- France -- 20th century.; Publishers and publishing -- France -- Paris -- 20th century.; World War, 1939-1945 -- France -- Paris.; Paris (France) -- History -- German occupation, 1940-1945.; Correspondence -- 20th century.; Photoprints.; American literature; European literature; European literature; Publishing history; American literature
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1901-1970; 39 boxes (1 partial)
  The correspondence series includes correspondence from and to Sylvia Beach. While this series largely encompasses Sylvia Beach's personal correspondence, previously interfiled business correspondence has been maintained in this file group. Correspondence with family members is interfiled.
  Correspondents of note include Hilda Doolittle, Ezra Pound, Sherwood Anderson, Gertrude Stein, Ernest Hemingway, Robert McAlmon, James Joyce, T. S. Eliot, William Carlos Williams, Allen Tate, Alice B. Toklas, Marianne Moore, Katherine Anne Porter, Richard Wright, George Antheil, Harriet Weaver, Gordon Craig, Arthur Symons, Ford Madox Ford, Frank Harris, Norman Douglas, Ivy Litvinoff, Richard Aldington, Stuart Gilbert, Cyril Connolly, D. H. Lawrence, Stephen Spender, Dorothy Richardson, and others.
  Researchers primarily interested in Sylvia Beach's business correspondence are advised also to consult the Shakespeare & Company series.
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondent and chronologically within.
  - Abécassis, Guy, 1959 November 29; 1 folder (Folder 1)
  - Abraham & Straus, Inc., 1927 November 10; 1 folder (Folder 2)
  - Acosta, Mercedes de, undated; 1 folder (Folder 3)
  - Adam, George, 1962 July 27; 1 folder (Folder 4)
  - Adams, E. C. L., 1927 June 14; 1 folder (Folder 5)
  - Adams, F. B. Jr., 1950 July 10; 1 folder (Folder 6)
  - Aggrey, O. Rudolph, 1959 May 5; 1 folder (Folder 7)
  - Aldington, Richard, 1929 January 2-1937 March 14; 1 folder (Folder 8)
  - Allen, D. M., 1953 August 22; 1 folder (Folder 9)
  - The American Library in Paris, 1946 June 18-1951 April 23; 2 folders (Folder 10-11)
  - The American Women's Group in Paris, 1952 January 14; 1 folder (Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Elbridge G., 1939 June 22; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    Includes an autograph manuscript of "Autobiography of Wonder: A Collection of Poetical Scratchings" sent by Elbridge Anderson to Sylvia Beach.
  - Anderson, Forrest, 1934 September 10; 1 folder (Folder 14)
  - Anderson, Margaret, 1937 March 27; 1 folder (Folder 15)
  - Anderson, Sherwood, 1921 December 3-1939 December 9; 1 folder (Folder 16)
  - Andrews, George, 1954 October 18-1957 September 7; 1 folder (Folder 17)
  - Aragon, Louis, undated; 1 folder (Folder 18)
  - Ardagh, John, undated; 1 folder (Folder 19)
  - Armes, Ethel, 1937 July 7; 1 folder (Folder 20)
  - Armitage, Jane, 1959 May 6; 1 folder (Folder 21)
  - Arnaud, Odette, 1959 November 30; 1 folder (Folder 22)
  - Arts Magazine, 1962 June 1; 1 folder (Folder 23)
  - Ashland, Arthur, 1928 March 27; 1 folder (Folder 24)
  - Ashworth, Roscoe, 1927 August 9; 1 folder (Folder 25)
  - Atkinson, Ruth A., 1951 May 9-November 11; 1 folder (Folder 26)
  - Auclair, Marcelle, 1961 December 19-1962 June 22; 1 folder (Folder 27)
  - Auden, W. H., 1957 January-March; 1 folder (Folder 28)
  - Aurousseau, M., 1927 October 21; 1 folder (Folder 29)
  - Aveline, Claude, 1922 October 9; 1 folder (Folder 30)
  - Antheil, Böske, 1925-1937; 1 folder (Folder 31)
  - Antheil, George, 1923-1938; 12 folders
    - Antheil, George, 1923; 1 folder (Folder 32)
    - Antheil, George, 1924; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      Regarding O'Neill incident.
    - Antheil, George, 1924; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      Includes letter to Sylvia Beach and note from Ernest Hemingway.
      Patrons to use surrogate copies in lieu of originals.
    - Antheil, George, 1925; 1 folder (Folder 35)
    - Antheil, George, 1926; 1 folder (Folder 36)
    - Antheil, George, 1927; 1 folder (Folder 37)
    - Antheil, George, 1928; 1 folder (Folder 38)
    - Antheil, George, 1929; 1 folder (Folder 39)
    - Antheil, George, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 40)
    - Antheil, George, 1932; 1 folder (Folder 41)
    - Antheil, George, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 42)
    - Antheil, George, undated; 1 folder (Folder 43)
  - Babbitt, Dora Drew, 1937 August 18; 1 folder (Folder 1)
  - Baker, Denys Val, 1946 July 13; 1 folder (Folder 2)
  - Bishop, Balogh, 1926; 1 folder (Folder 3)
  - Baldwin, Frederick, undated; 1 folder (Folder 4)
  - Baldwin, Helen (Mrs. James), 1928-1954; 1 folder (Folder 5)
  - Baltrusaitis, Hélène, 1958 July 9-1962 September 7; 1 folder (Folder 6)
  - Barkey, I. H., 1928 February 19; 1 folder (Folder 7)
  - Barnes, Djuna, 1962 September 7; 1 folder (Folder 8)
  - Barney, Natalie Clifford, 1937 January 7-1954 December 20; 1 folder (Folder 9)
  - Barrie Books Ltd., 1959 March 23; 1 folder (Folder 10)
  - Bartlett, Francis, 1950 July 4; 1 folder (Folder 11)
  - Bartlett, Henrietta C., undated; 1 folder (Folder 12)
  - Bataille, Alfred, 1959 March 27; 1 folder (Folder 13)
  - Bates, Ernest S., undated; 1 folder (Folder 14)
  - Battle, E. G., 1962 August 12-September 28; 1 folder (Folder 15)
  - Baudot, Jeanne, 1946 March 26; 1 folder (Folder 16)
  - Beach, Edward W. to Sylvia Beach, 1932-1933; 1 folder (Folder 17)
  - Beach, Emma Virginia, 1928-1934; 2 folders
    - Beach, Emma to Sylvia Beach, 1928-1934; 1 folder (Folder 18)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Emma Beach, 1931; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      Added to Sylvia Beach Collection by Holly Beach Dennis in 1966.
  - Beach, Helen, 1959; 2 folders
    - Beach, Helen to Sylvia Beach, 1959; 1 folder (Folder 20)
    - Beach, Helen to Sylvia Beach, undated; 1 folder (Folder 21)
  - Beach, Sylvester W., 1912-1940; 3 boxes (2 partial)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach and Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1912-1916; 1 folder (Folder 22)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1914-1919; 1 folder (Folder 23)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach and Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1916; 1 folder (Folder 24)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach and Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1917; 1 folder (Folder 25)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1917; 1 folder (Folder 26)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1918; 1 folder (Folder 27)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach and Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1918-1920; 1 folder (Folder 28)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1919; 1 folder (Folder 29)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1921; 1 folder (Folder 30)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1922; 1 folder (Folder 31)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach and Holly Beach, 1922-1925; 1 folder (Folder 32)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1923; 1 folder (Folder 33)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach, 1926-1929; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1928; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1929; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach, 1930-1932; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1931; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1932; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1933; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach, 1933; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1934; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach and Holly Beach, 1934; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1935; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1936; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach, 1936-1938; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1937; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 16)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach, Sylvester W. to Sylvia Beach, 1940; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Sylvester W. Beach, 1940; 1 folder (Folder 4)
  - Beach, Eleanor O., 1911-1927; portions of 2 boxes
    - Beach, Eleanor O. to Sylvia Beach, 1911; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach, Eleanor O. to Sylvia Beach, 1915; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach, Eleanor O. to Sylvia Beach, 1916; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Beach, Eleanor O. to Sylvia Beach, 1917; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Beach, Eleanor O. to Sylvia Beach, 1917; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Beach, Eleanor O. to Sylvia Beach, 1917; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1917; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Beach, Eleanor O. to Sylvia Beach, 1918-1919; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      Includes first check mailed by Eleanor Beach for opening of Shakespeare & Company.
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1919; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1919 August 27; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      Regarding the opening of the bookshop.
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1920; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1921; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1922; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1923; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1924; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1925; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Beach, Eleanor O. to Sylvia Beach, 1919-1926; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1926; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1926; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor O. Beach, 1927; 1 folder (Folder 11)
  - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian), 1913-1951; portions of 2 boxes
    - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian) to Sylvia Beach, 1913-1916; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1913-1917; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1914; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach from Madrid, 1916; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian) to Sylvia Beach, 1917; 1 folder (Folder 16)
    - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian) to Sylvia Beach, 1918-1919; 1 folder (Folder 17)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1919; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian) to Sylvia Beach, 1920-1929; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian) to Sylvia Beach, 1930-1933; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1930; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1932; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Eleanor (Cyprian) Beach, 1933; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian) to Sylvia Beach, 1934-1936; portion of 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian) to Sylvia Beach, 1937-1939; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian) to Sylvia Beach, 1940-1947; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Beach, Eleanor (Cyprian) to Sylvia Beach, 1948-1951; 1 folder (Folder 10)
  - Beach (Dennis), Holly, 1915-1962; 7 boxes (2 partial)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1915; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1916; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1917; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1917; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Beach (Dennis), Hollyh to Sylvia Beach, 1918; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1918; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1919; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1920; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1920-1922; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1921; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1921 April 23; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      Concerning the Publication of Ulysses.
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1924; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1925-1929; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1925; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1926; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1926; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1927; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1928; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1929; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1930; 1 folder (Folder 16)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1930-1932; 1 folder (Folder 17)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1931; 1 folder (Folder 18)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1932; 1 folder (Folder 19)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1933; 1 folder (Folder 20)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1933; 1 folder (Folder 21)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1934; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1934; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1935; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1936; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1937; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1938; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1938; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1939; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1939; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1940; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1940-1945; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1942-1944; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1945; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1946; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 16)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1947; 1 folder (Folder 17)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1948; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1949; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1950; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1951; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1952; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1953; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1954; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1955; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1956; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1959; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1959; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1960; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1960; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1961; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1961; 1 folder (Folder 3-4)
      Regarding Stocks.
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1961; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Beach (Dennis), Holly to Sylvia Beach, 1962; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Beach, Sylvia to Holly Beach (Dennis), 1962; 1 folder (Folder 7)